<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Asia on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</title>
    <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tags/asia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Asia on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-SG</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2019 Hazrul Azhar</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 02:34:33 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//www.hazrulazhar.com/tags/asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a collaborative user network for Open Source WordPress in Asia</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/building-a-collaborative-user-network-for-open-source-wordpress-in-asia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 02:34:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/building-a-collaborative-user-network-for-open-source-wordpress-in-asia/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
Ladies and Gentlemen
Esteemed guests, from Singapore and overseas.
Thank you very much for helping us make history. You are the first attendees to Singapore&#39;s inaugural WordCamp.
Before I begin, I would like you to spend a moment asking yourselves this question. Why are you here? What are you doing right now? Are you blogging? Updating your Facebook? Sending a tweet? Checking in? What are you doing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menyerah Mahkota</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/menyerah-mahkota/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 04:00:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/menyerah-mahkota/</guid>
      <description>Every morning reciting the pledge, repeating every word, instilled in me a belief of the greatness of this nation. When I grew up, everywhere I turned, I had friends of different races and faiths. I could go to the mainstream PAP kindergarten in the mornings and I also went to the mosque kindergarten in the afternoon. I was exposed to different customs and languages and I had the opportunity to bask in the rich multi-racial flavour of our nation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanah Tumpah Darah</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tanah-tumpah-darah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 04:06:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tanah-tumpah-darah/</guid>
      <description>Marker at the entrance of Bukit Chandu memorial
Second Lieutenant Adnan Bin Saidi.
Lieutenant Abdullah Bin Saad.
Lieutenant Ariffin Bin Haji Sulaiman.
Lieutenant Ibrahim Bin Sidek.
Lieutenant Abdul Wahid Bin Mat Kidam.
These are just some of the names that no one knows, who fought, bled and died for this land. These are the officers of the Malay Regiment. These are the anak watan who lived a short life, but left a great legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>