<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reflections on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</title>
    <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tags/reflections/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reflections on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-SG</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2019 Hazrul Azhar</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 05:27:33 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//www.hazrulazhar.com/tags/reflections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>National Day - A celebration of what exactly?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/national-day-a-celebration-of-what-exactly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 05:27:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/national-day-a-celebration-of-what-exactly/</guid>
      <description>In order to build our future, we need to understand our past. Singapore never proclaimed independence from Malaysia, a territory it fought to unite with. On the other hand, the 9th of August was a result of PM Tunku Abdul Rahman&amp;rsquo;s convictions that the internal security of Malaysia required Singapore&amp;rsquo;s exit. PM Lee Kuan Yew did not rejoice on the 9th of August 1965. On the other hand, he wept, publicly, live on television.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will You?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/will-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2007 04:52:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/will-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ah yes. I know this is going to be a &lt;em&gt;basi&lt;/em&gt; entry. But I had a commitment to write this. I&#39;d like to share with my international friends, the story of this little red dot (as popularised by former Indonesian Head-of-State, President Habibie), on our &lt;a title=&#34;NDP 2007 Website&#34; href=&#34;http://www.ndp.org.sg/&#34;&gt;42nd year of independence&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I watched the spectacular &lt;a title=&#34;Watch NDP on demand!&#34; href=&#34;http://www.ndp.org.sg/multimedia/webcast/index.html&#34;&gt;celebrations from home on the Internet&lt;/a&gt;. Before I left for Jakarta, honestly, I didn&#39;t see much in Singapore that I wanted to be associated with. I would prefer a life in Australia (I still do). But coming home from Indonesia helped me to better appreciate the little things I put up with growing up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone size-full wp-image-442&#34; src=&#34;//www.hazrulazhar.com/uploads/2007/09/dsc000581.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;384&#34; height=&#34;512&#34; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Packed road leading to Marina Bay&lt;a title=&#34;Packed road leading to Marina Bay&#34; href=&#34;http://hazrulazhar.com/wp-content/uploads/2007/09/dsc00058.JPG&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>