<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>singapore on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</title>
    <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tags/singapore/</link>
    <description>Recent content in singapore on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-SG</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2019 Hazrul Azhar</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 02:34:33 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//www.hazrulazhar.com/tags/singapore/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a collaborative user network for Open Source WordPress in Asia</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/building-a-collaborative-user-network-for-open-source-wordpress-in-asia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 02:34:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/building-a-collaborative-user-network-for-open-source-wordpress-in-asia/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
Ladies and Gentlemen
Esteemed guests, from Singapore and overseas.
Thank you very much for helping us make history. You are the first attendees to Singapore&#39;s inaugural WordCamp.
Before I begin, I would like you to spend a moment asking yourselves this question. Why are you here? What are you doing right now? Are you blogging? Updating your Facebook? Sending a tweet? Checking in? What are you doing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menyerah Mahkota</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/menyerah-mahkota/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 04:00:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/menyerah-mahkota/</guid>
      <description>Every morning reciting the pledge, repeating every word, instilled in me a belief of the greatness of this nation. When I grew up, everywhere I turned, I had friends of different races and faiths. I could go to the mainstream PAP kindergarten in the mornings and I also went to the mosque kindergarten in the afternoon. I was exposed to different customs and languages and I had the opportunity to bask in the rich multi-racial flavour of our nation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demi Tanahair</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/demi-tanahair/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 04:46:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/demi-tanahair/</guid>
      <description>The last stand
The enemy shelled relentlessly. &#34;Tuan! Peluru dah habis tuan!&#34;, shouted a private. Charlie company had ran out of ammo. Lieutenant Adnan knew the inevitable. They were outnumbered 10 to 1. The 1st and 2nd Regiment gave everything they had, frustrating the Japs, pushing them back to Reformatory Road. But the moment of no return had come. Lieutenant Adnan had a choice to make. It would be untruthful to say that he was glad to make that choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanah Tumpah Darah</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tanah-tumpah-darah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 04:06:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tanah-tumpah-darah/</guid>
      <description>Marker at the entrance of Bukit Chandu memorial
Second Lieutenant Adnan Bin Saidi.
Lieutenant Abdullah Bin Saad.
Lieutenant Ariffin Bin Haji Sulaiman.
Lieutenant Ibrahim Bin Sidek.
Lieutenant Abdul Wahid Bin Mat Kidam.
These are just some of the names that no one knows, who fought, bled and died for this land. These are the officers of the Malay Regiment. These are the anak watan who lived a short life, but left a great legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singaporean enough?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singaporean-enough/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 18:39:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singaporean-enough/</guid>
      <description>When I go to the coffeeshop to order a cup of coke, I am greeted by a China-girl, who can&#39;t speak an inch of English, and tried to mouth back my order in barely comprehensible mainland Mandarin. The local prata shop staff which resides in the coffeeshop, is constantly frustrated at her, to the point of bad-mouthing in terms I can only say are ungracious. They&#39;ve tried so hard to communicate, telling her in English, that the used plates are to be placed inside the bin, not on their counters, but to no avail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halal - Another Feared Idea</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/halal-another-feared-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 22:14:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/halal-another-feared-idea/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A tale of 3 people from 3 nations</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-tale-of-3-people-from-3-nations-ethnicity-and-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 22:14:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-tale-of-3-people-from-3-nations-ethnicity-and-culture/</guid>
      <description>This would be a basi entry coz Ramadan was so 5 days ago. But I wanted to blog about the time I spent roaming around Geylang with Crystal and her friends. The only reason why I had not written about it was because I didn&#39;t snap enough good pics on those days, and for the life of me, I can&#39;t seem to remember one of her friend&#39;s name.
But I&#39;ll write about it anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Prayer Places Locater Screencast</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singapore-prayer-places-locater-screencast.html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2007 05:21:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singapore-prayer-places-locater-screencast.html/</guid>
      <description>Now I&#39;ve been getting questions about this app. Everyone&#39;s wondering where can they find it. The bad news is, not so soon. I don&#39;t have a place to host this yet. The good news is, I created a screencast so that people can preview the power of Google Maps + a little bit of ingenuity from yours truly.
I hope this video will help you to visualise what SPPL is about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Prayer Places Locater 1.0 Beta Preview</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singapore-prayer-places-locater-10-beta-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 05:34:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singapore-prayer-places-locater-10-beta-preview/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve finished coding SPPL version 1.0. This is the Beta which I completed in a matter of 3 or 4 days. This application allows the user to search for the nearest mosque or musolla from his specified location. If you&#39;re a forgetful klutz like I am, or get intimidated by tall buildings or is in a huff but is not familliar with the area and so have no idea where the nearest prayer place is, SPPL is for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday at a quaint little mosque in Eunos</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/friday-at-a-quaint-little-mosque-in-eunos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 01:17:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/friday-at-a-quaint-little-mosque-in-eunos/</guid>
      <description>I find that I know so little about Singapore and it&#39;s hidden finds. Last Friday, I had my Friday prayers in a little known mosque hidden deep inside the private estates of Eunos. Masjid Al Abdul Razak appears to be a mosque of much history, with a architecture that resembles Yemeni/Saudi culture fused with less modern materials like zinc for a rustic, kampong feel.
Masjid Al Abdul Razak, a priceless heritage</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will You?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/will-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2007 04:52:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/will-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ah yes. I know this is going to be a &lt;em&gt;basi&lt;/em&gt; entry. But I had a commitment to write this. I&#39;d like to share with my international friends, the story of this little red dot (as popularised by former Indonesian Head-of-State, President Habibie), on our &lt;a title=&#34;NDP 2007 Website&#34; href=&#34;http://www.ndp.org.sg/&#34;&gt;42nd year of independence&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I watched the spectacular &lt;a title=&#34;Watch NDP on demand!&#34; href=&#34;http://www.ndp.org.sg/multimedia/webcast/index.html&#34;&gt;celebrations from home on the Internet&lt;/a&gt;. Before I left for Jakarta, honestly, I didn&#39;t see much in Singapore that I wanted to be associated with. I would prefer a life in Australia (I still do). But coming home from Indonesia helped me to better appreciate the little things I put up with growing up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone size-full wp-image-442&#34; src=&#34;//www.hazrulazhar.com/uploads/2007/09/dsc000581.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;384&#34; height=&#34;512&#34; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Packed road leading to Marina Bay&lt;a title=&#34;Packed road leading to Marina Bay&#34; href=&#34;http://hazrulazhar.com/wp-content/uploads/2007/09/dsc00058.JPG&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>