<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>malaysia on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</title>
    <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tags/malaysia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in malaysia on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-SG</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2019 Hazrul Azhar</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 17:02:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//www.hazrulazhar.com/tags/malaysia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Young and Malay: Growing up in Multicultural Malaysia</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/young-and-malay-growing-up-in-multicultural-malaysia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 17:02:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/young-and-malay-growing-up-in-multicultural-malaysia/</guid>
      <description>Edited by Ooi Kee Beng and Wan Hamidi Hamid, this book is a collection of essays, some anecdotal, others academic, of the viewpoints of ordinary Malaysians who identify themselves as Malay, on their life stories that shaped their perspectives in growing up in a multi-cultural nation, whilst coming to terms with their ethnic identity that forces them into boxes.
I picked up this book in Penang, at the GerakBudaya bookstore, apparently quite famous among those who read Malaysian literature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menyerah Mahkota</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/menyerah-mahkota/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 04:00:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/menyerah-mahkota/</guid>
      <description>Every morning reciting the pledge, repeating every word, instilled in me a belief of the greatness of this nation. When I grew up, everywhere I turned, I had friends of different races and faiths. I could go to the mainstream PAP kindergarten in the mornings and I also went to the mosque kindergarten in the afternoon. I was exposed to different customs and languages and I had the opportunity to bask in the rich multi-racial flavour of our nation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A tale of 3 people from 3 nations</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-tale-of-3-people-from-3-nations-ethnicity-and-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 22:14:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-tale-of-3-people-from-3-nations-ethnicity-and-culture/</guid>
      <description>This would be a basi entry coz Ramadan was so 5 days ago. But I wanted to blog about the time I spent roaming around Geylang with Crystal and her friends. The only reason why I had not written about it was because I didn&#39;t snap enough good pics on those days, and for the life of me, I can&#39;t seem to remember one of her friend&#39;s name.
But I&#39;ll write about it anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>