<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>malay on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</title>
    <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tags/malay/</link>
    <description>Recent content in malay on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-SG</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 16:18:18 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//www.hazrulazhar.com/tags/malay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Malays represented as President, or a President that represents all?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/malays-represented-as-president-or-a-president-that-represents-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 16:18:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/malays-represented-as-president-or-a-president-that-represents-all/</guid>
      <description>Several years ago I shared how the government would back a Malay candidate for President after Nathan. The 2011 PE was an all Tan affair. However, the recent EP Commission has made clear the government&#39;s intention of a minority president from time to time.
Traditionally, Speakers of Parliament would likely be proposed as presidential candidates. Thus, since Abdullah Tarmugi and Halimah Yaacob&#39;s appointments as Speaker, I had been expecting one of them to be backed by government as their choice for President.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melayu. Who are you?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/melayu-who-are-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 02:06:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/melayu-who-are-you/</guid>
      <description>Melayu. Who are you?
Bongkok atau Bebas?
Radikal atau Alim?
Riau atau Baku?
Mundur atau Maju?
Yang aku tahu, Melayu bukan satu.
Kau Melayu. Aku Melayu. Tapi samakah kita?
Kau pukul satu. Aku pukul dua.
Tak bertemu-temu. Kerana janji Melayu.
Aku Melayu sini. Kau Melayu sana.
Kau belajar di Singapura, tapi tetap jiwa Alor Setar.
Kau Melayu miskin. Aku Melayu fakir.
Melayu kaya? Oh. Dia anak pemerintah saja.
Aku Melayu terdidik.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menyerah Mahkota</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/menyerah-mahkota/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 04:00:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/menyerah-mahkota/</guid>
      <description>Every morning reciting the pledge, repeating every word, instilled in me a belief of the greatness of this nation. When I grew up, everywhere I turned, I had friends of different races and faiths. I could go to the mainstream PAP kindergarten in the mornings and I also went to the mosque kindergarten in the afternoon. I was exposed to different customs and languages and I had the opportunity to bask in the rich multi-racial flavour of our nation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A tale of 3 people from 3 nations</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-tale-of-3-people-from-3-nations-ethnicity-and-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 22:14:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-tale-of-3-people-from-3-nations-ethnicity-and-culture/</guid>
      <description>This would be a basi entry coz Ramadan was so 5 days ago. But I wanted to blog about the time I spent roaming around Geylang with Crystal and her friends. The only reason why I had not written about it was because I didn&#39;t snap enough good pics on those days, and for the life of me, I can&#39;t seem to remember one of her friend&#39;s name.
But I&#39;ll write about it anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>