<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hazrul Azhar Jamari on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</title>
    <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hazrul Azhar Jamari on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-SG</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2019 Hazrul Azhar</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:30:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//www.hazrulazhar.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Man</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/family-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:30:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/family-man/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m married to Farah Nadia, a passionate educator in the Singapore Civil Service. Together, we are parents to our adorable son, Rafa Shakur, and cat parents to rescue cats Rachael, Shiro and Abu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Learning Material</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/python-learning-material/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/python-learning-material/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been on a learning journey and just picking up Python properly. It isn&amp;rsquo;t the first time I was introduced to Python or Django. My ex-colleague, Hong introduced it to me ages ago back in 2008. That was also when Django started. I was still very much a PHP man then. Still is now. At my current company, Python is used heavily. The syntax is similar to Ruby, but somehow has a PHP feel to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fight vs Flight</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/fight-v-flight/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/fight-v-flight/</guid>
      <description>Young people sometimes ask me what does it take to build a business. I&amp;rsquo;ve been in startups almost all my adult life. Some I built, others I was part of. My collective experience has taught me the following practical truth bombs.
  You will always have to maintain someone. If you&amp;rsquo;re not married, as Asians, you will normally live with your parents. You will need to contribute to the household one way or another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 12:29:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Community</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tech-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 12:10:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tech-community/</guid>
      <description>Speak WordCamp Singapore 2019
Comparing WooCommerce SaaS vs Managed Woocommerce Hosting - WordCamp Singapore 2019
WordCamp Singapore 2017
How WooCommerce is being disrupted by Shopify.
BarCamp JB 2015
How to sell online faster by not building a website.
BarCamp Singapore 2011
Growth of WordPress 2011.
WordCamp Singapore 2011
Building a collaborative user network for Open Source WordPress in Asia.
Volunteer DevSG Telegram Community, 2018 - Present Founded the DevSG telegram groups playing the role as Servant-Leader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foodie</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/foodie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 04:18:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/foodie/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m an avid foodie and post (not so) daily on Instagram/@haz_daily and Facebook/@hazdaily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halalonclick, WhatsHalal gabung teroka pasaran baru</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/halalonclick-whatshalal-gabung-teroka-pasaran-baru/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/halalonclick-whatshalal-gabung-teroka-pasaran-baru/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch of GeoWorks - Singapore&#39;s Geospatial Industry Centre</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/launch-of-geoworks-singapore-s-geospatial-industry-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/launch-of-geoworks-singapore-s-geospatial-industry-centre/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to redirect everything to a new domain except root page and WP directories for WordPress sites</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2018-06-27-how-to-redirect-everything-to-a-new-domain-except-root-page-and-wp-directories-for-wordpress-sites/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 23:24:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2018-06-27-how-to-redirect-everything-to-a-new-domain-except-root-page-and-wp-directories-for-wordpress-sites/</guid>
      <description>If you ever run a WordPress site that was going to be decomissioned, and you needed to redirect everything to the new domain running a non-WordPress site to the new domain&amp;rsquo;s root page, but you do not want to redirect the root page of your old domain and any WordPress directories, spare 2 hours of your life and 10 varieties of cuss words. Here&amp;rsquo;s your answer.
Remove the following code in your .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Usahawan - Berita palsu boleh jejas hubungan masyarakat, ada libatkan isu Sunni-Syiah</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/usahawan-berita-palsu-boleh-jejas-hubungan-masyarakat-ada-libatkan-isu-sunni-syiah/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/usahawan-berita-palsu-boleh-jejas-hubungan-masyarakat-ada-libatkan-isu-sunni-syiah/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bukan hanya tanggungjawab pemerintah tangani isu kepalsuan online disengajakan</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/bukan-hanya-tanggungjawab-pemerintah-tangani-isu-kepalsuan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/bukan-hanya-tanggungjawab-pemerintah-tangani-isu-kepalsuan/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sebenar.my mentioned at Singapore’s public hearing on deliberate online falsehoods</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/sebenar-my-mentioned-at-singapores-public-hearing-on-deliberate-online-falsehoods/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/sebenar-my-mentioned-at-singapores-public-hearing-on-deliberate-online-falsehoods/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TradeGecko hosts the Singapore Shopify Meetup in November 2017</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/shopify-meetup-singapore-nov2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/shopify-meetup-singapore-nov2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The amazing people streets at Teacher&#39;s Estate are named after</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-08-29-the-amazing-people-streets-at-teachers-estate-are-named-after/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 23:30:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-08-29-the-amazing-people-streets-at-teachers-estate-are-named-after/</guid>
      <description>The Teacher&#39;s Estate is a private housing estate, named so because it was an area where government school teachers lived. This area have very interesting street names. All of the street names were named after an Asian philosopher and poet. In total, there are 7 historical figures that the roads were named after. Here&#39;s a list of them.
Omar Khayyam Avenue - named after Ghiyath ad-Din Abu I-Fath Omar Ibn Ibrahim Khayyam Neishapuri also known as Omar Khayyam</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solution to when none of your Mac accounts work and you can&#39;t login to your computer</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-08-29-solution-to-when-none-of-your-mac-accounts-work-and-you-cant-login-to-your-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 16:54:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-08-29-solution-to-when-none-of-your-mac-accounts-work-and-you-cant-login-to-your-computer/</guid>
      <description>So I had a very peculiar problem yesterday when I had to setup a Mac for a new user. The only problem was, I could not login to the admin account. That was strange. We provision accounts remotely using JumpCloud, allowing user credentials to be provisioned to individual systems. It allows me greater efficiency to onboard and offboard users.
What happened was the Mac has been inactive for 5 months. For some reason, it couldn&#39;t validate my password even though it was the correct one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progressing with Tech</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-08-15-progressing-with-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 11:06:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-08-15-progressing-with-tech/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been invited as a Table Host where I&#39;ll answer your questions about the Tech industry one-to-one, this Saturday, 19 August 2017, 10am-1.30pm.
Suitable for students, fresh graduates, working adults, mid-career professionals, stay-at-home mothers, anyone and everyone keen to learn more about tech! PPIS is working with The Codette Project to highlight the ease of access into the world of technology for your personal and professional use.
Apart from myself as a Table Host, there will also be a Panel Discussion with Member of Parliament, Mr Saktiandi Supaat and some of my friends from the Tech Industry, Liyana Sulaiman (Gimmie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordCamp Singapore 2017</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-07-27-20171028-wordcamp-singapore-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 15:03:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-07-27-20171028-wordcamp-singapore-2017/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve submitted my proposal to speak at WordCamp Singapore 2017 and hopefully accepted, I&#39;ll give insights into the State of the Woo regionally and globally.
Date: Saturday, 28 October 2017
Time: TBC
Venue: Suntec City Convention Centre
Topic Title: How WooCommerce is being disrupted by Shopify and why it will rapidly lose market share
Topic Description: WooCommerce is the most deployed eCommerce shopping cart platform in the world. But catching up closely is the world&#39;s most popular hosted eCommerce shopping cart - Shopify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduates Tea 2017</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-07-27-20170820-graduates-tea-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 00:05:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-07-27-20170820-graduates-tea-2017/</guid>
      <description>Date: Sunday, 20 August 2017
10.30am to 2.30pm
Convention Centre@Suntec City
Register here: https://www.eventbrite.sg/e/mendaki-club-graduates-tea-2017-registration-35432282912
I&#39;ve been invited as a Table Host and will be sharing my experiences as an entrepreneur, technologist and E-Commerce hero. I&#39;ll help answer your questions about business and entrepreneurship, the software engineer career and E-Commerce insights. Feel free to give me an elevator pitch. Alongside me will be my wife, who is also invited as a Table Host, and she will be sharing her experiences as an educator, civil servant, and scholar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start With Why</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-06-15-start-with-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 16:13:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-06-15-start-with-why/</guid>
      <description>Great concept. I apply it in my daily life. The book seems to reiterate the Why in every chapter though. There is some extrapolation of the Golden Circle but it keeps coming back to Why. Probably the author&#39;s way of emphasising it&#39;s importance.
The stories are a bit long and may seem to look like fluff. But there&#39;s actually meat on this book. Just that the simple concept would take better articulation to present its points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standards Adoption Workshop - TR46:2016 Last Mile Delivery - eCommerce Data Interchange</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-05-25-20170524-standards-adoption-workshop-tr462016-last-mile-delivery-ecommerce-data-interchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 16:09:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-05-25-20170524-standards-adoption-workshop-tr462016-last-mile-delivery-ecommerce-data-interchange/</guid>
      <description>I was the final speaker for the workshop standing among other contemporaries in the Logistics Tech industry. I recounted our experience adopting the TR46 standard into our TMS and elaborated the productivity gains as a result of the standards adoption. Many attendees later asked me questions on adopting the standards and the application of last mile technology in their processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a company with the right values</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-02-05-building-a-company-with-the-right-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 00:08:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-02-05-building-a-company-with-the-right-values/</guid>
      <description>To determine the company&#39;s success, it&#39;s not the technology or the team you assemble that matters most. Having built 4 businesses before and being part of 3 startups, my observations and experiences have made me discover that a company&#39;s values are what will make a company successful.
As an employee, one might not care about a company&#39;s mission, vision and values. It may seem like a piece of decoration and never taken seriously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deen &amp; Dunia - Designing bright Muslim professionals by Brothers of NUS</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/deen-dunia-designing-bright-muslim-professionals-by-brothers-of-nus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 22:44:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/deen-dunia-designing-bright-muslim-professionals-by-brothers-of-nus/</guid>
      <description>Venue: LT33 @ S17
The Prophet Muhammad (p.b.u.h) was asked what type of earning was best, and he replied, “A man’s work with his hands and every (lawful) business transaction.”
Entrepreneurs play an important role in our society, especially if one were to go back to the times of the Sahabahs and the Golden Age of Islam. However, in today’s day and age, being an entrepreneur, especially for a Muslim, is rarely an option when looking at a career path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Young and Malay: Growing up in Multicultural Malaysia</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/young-and-malay-growing-up-in-multicultural-malaysia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 17:02:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/young-and-malay-growing-up-in-multicultural-malaysia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career&#43;Tech Workshop by Mendaki Club</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-02-04-careertech-workshop-by-mendaki-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 22:26:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-02-04-careertech-workshop-by-mendaki-club/</guid>
      <description>Saturday, December 10, 2016
10am to 12pm
IMDA Labs@NDC
REGISTER TODAY: https://goo.gl/forms/GMa6frKNC2UYK1v73
Career+Tech explores how technology has impacted today&#39;s career landscape and how we can ride the &#34;tech wave&#34;.
Programme:
[1000-1040] Hands-on Activity by iCommerce Asia
&amp;gt; Learn the inner workings of the E-commerce supply chain from click to doorstep, through an interactive hands-on session by iCommerce Asia.
[1040-1100] Social Discussion by VoidDeck Ventures
&amp;gt; Together with tech enthusiasts, discuss how one can enhance their professional skill sets, and help the community embrace technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMP Learning Festival</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-02-04-20161022-amp-learning-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 22:53:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-02-04-20161022-amp-learning-festival/</guid>
      <description>Date: Saturday, 22nd October 2016
Venue: Singapore University of Technology and Design
I will be sharing my life experience of starting a business in the technology world with school students ages 11 and up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malays represented as President, or a President that represents all?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/malays-represented-as-president-or-a-president-that-represents-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 16:18:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/malays-represented-as-president-or-a-president-that-represents-all/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Startups By Muslims In Singapore You Need To Know This Ramadhan</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/7-muslim-startups-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2016 13:49:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/7-muslim-startups-singapore/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing Intelligently</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/pricing-intelligently/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 13:26:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/pricing-intelligently/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons to ensure success for mobile payments in SE Asia.</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/lessons-to-ensure-success-for-mobile-payments-in-se-asia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 23:46:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/lessons-to-ensure-success-for-mobile-payments-in-se-asia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My experience applying for MaGiC&#39;s MAP</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/my-experience-applying-for-magics-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 11:31:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/my-experience-applying-for-magics-map/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More public holidays may be better</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/more-public-holidays-may-be-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/more-public-holidays-may-be-better/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HalalOnClick, a halal food delivery service in Singapore.</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/halalonclick-com-a-halal-food-delivery-service-in-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:37:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/halalonclick-com-a-halal-food-delivery-service-in-singapore/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Day - A celebration of what exactly?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/national-day-a-celebration-of-what-exactly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 05:27:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/national-day-a-celebration-of-what-exactly/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Singapore&#39;s media should be the backbone of local football</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/why-singapores-media-should-be-the-backbone-of-local-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 11:53:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/why-singapores-media-should-be-the-backbone-of-local-football/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a collaborative user network for Open Source WordPress in Asia</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/building-a-collaborative-user-network-for-open-source-wordpress-in-asia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 02:34:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/building-a-collaborative-user-network-for-open-source-wordpress-in-asia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A public declaration of love</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-public-declaration-of-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 05:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-public-declaration-of-love/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melayu. Who are you?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/melayu-who-are-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 02:06:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/melayu-who-are-you/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menyerah Mahkota</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/menyerah-mahkota/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 04:00:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/menyerah-mahkota/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demi Tanahair</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/demi-tanahair/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 04:46:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/demi-tanahair/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanah Tumpah Darah</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tanah-tumpah-darah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 04:06:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tanah-tumpah-darah/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Islamic Information with iAlif</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/get-islamic-information-with-ialif/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/get-islamic-information-with-ialif/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singaporean enough?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singaporean-enough/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 18:39:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singaporean-enough/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Malay Story</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/the-malay-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2009 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/the-malay-story/</guid>
      <description>The following is a speech I gave in the presence of attendees of the &amp;ldquo;Melayu 2.0&amp;rdquo; meetup, an interest group supported by Mendaki that sought to engage the community to write a better future for Singapore Malays.
Dear friends.
In the past 10 years of Malay history, our community has seen through many challenges that has made our progress difficult and minute. When we ask ourselves, what has the Malay people achieved, there is little that we can be proud of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halal - Another Feared Idea</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/halal-another-feared-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 22:14:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/halal-another-feared-idea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A tale of 3 people from 3 nations</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-tale-of-3-people-from-3-nations-ethnicity-and-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 22:14:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-tale-of-3-people-from-3-nations-ethnicity-and-culture/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Prayer Places Locater Screencast</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singapore-prayer-places-locater-screencast.html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2007 05:21:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singapore-prayer-places-locater-screencast.html/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Prayer Places Locater 1.0 Beta Preview</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singapore-prayer-places-locater-10-beta-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 05:34:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singapore-prayer-places-locater-10-beta-preview/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally getting the hang of Ruby on Rails</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/finally-getting-the-hang-of-ruby-on-rails/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2007 03:38:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/finally-getting-the-hang-of-ruby-on-rails/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday at a quaint little mosque in Eunos</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/friday-at-a-quaint-little-mosque-in-eunos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 01:17:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/friday-at-a-quaint-little-mosque-in-eunos/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will You?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/will-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2007 04:52:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/will-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>