<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hazrul Azhar Jamari on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</title>
    <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hazrul Azhar Jamari on Hazrul Azhar Jamari. Technopreneur based in Singapore.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-SG</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2019 Hazrul Azhar</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 12:29:12 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//www.hazrulazhar.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 12:29:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/contact/</guid>
      <description> Your Name:   Your Email:   Your Subject:   Message:   Send  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Community</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tech-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 12:10:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tech-community/</guid>
      <description>Speak WordCamp Singapore 2017
How WooCommerce is being disrupted by Shopify.
BarCamp JB 2015
How to sell online faster by not building a website.
BarCamp Singapore 2011
Growth of WordPress 2011.
WordCamp Singapore 2011
Building a collaborative user network for Open Source WordPress in Asia.
Volunteer Singapore WordPress User Group, 2010 - 2011
Lead Co-Founder of WordPress User Group organising bi-monthly meetups. partnering with the NLB and co-working spaces. Today, I attend meetups occasionally as a regular member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foodie</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/foodie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 04:18:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/foodie/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m an avid foodie and post daily on Instagram/@haz_daily and Facebook/@hazdaily. Sometimes, I give my honest reviews on restaurants I visit on Instagram/@honesthalalreviews and Facebook/@honesthalalreviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Family Man</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/family-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 03:13:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/family-man/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m married to Farah Nadia, a passionate educator in the Singapore Civil Service. Together, we are cat parents to rescue cats Rachael, Shiro and Abu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halalonclick, WhatsHalal gabung teroka pasaran baru</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/halalonclick-whatshalal-gabung-teroka-pasaran-baru/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/halalonclick-whatshalal-gabung-teroka-pasaran-baru/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch of GeoWorks - Singapore&#39;s Geospatial Industry Centre</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/launch-of-geoworks-singapore-s-geospatial-industry-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/launch-of-geoworks-singapore-s-geospatial-industry-centre/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to redirect everything to a new domain except root page and WP directories for WordPress sites</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2018-06-27-how-to-redirect-everything-to-a-new-domain-except-root-page-and-wp-directories-for-wordpress-sites/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 23:24:15 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2018-06-27-how-to-redirect-everything-to-a-new-domain-except-root-page-and-wp-directories-for-wordpress-sites/</guid>
      <description>If you ever run a WordPress site that was going to be decomissioned, and you needed to redirect everything to the new domain running a non-WordPress site to the new domain&amp;rsquo;s root page, but you do not want to redirect the root page of your old domain and any WordPress directories, spare 2 hours of your life and 10 varieties of cuss words. Here&amp;rsquo;s your answer.
Remove the following code in your .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Usahawan - Berita palsu boleh jejas hubungan masyarakat, ada libatkan isu Sunni-Syiah</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/usahawan-berita-palsu-boleh-jejas-hubungan-masyarakat-ada-libatkan-isu-sunni-syiah/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/usahawan-berita-palsu-boleh-jejas-hubungan-masyarakat-ada-libatkan-isu-sunni-syiah/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bukan hanya tanggungjawab pemerintah tangani isu kepalsuan online disengajakan</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/bukan-hanya-tanggungjawab-pemerintah-tangani-isu-kepalsuan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/bukan-hanya-tanggungjawab-pemerintah-tangani-isu-kepalsuan/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sebenar.my mentioned at Singapore’s public hearing on deliberate online falsehoods</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/sebenar-my-mentioned-at-singapores-public-hearing-on-deliberate-online-falsehoods/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/sebenar-my-mentioned-at-singapores-public-hearing-on-deliberate-online-falsehoods/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TradeGecko hosts the Singapore Shopify Meetup in November 2017</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/shopify-meetup-singapore-nov2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/shopify-meetup-singapore-nov2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The amazing people streets at Teacher&#39;s Estate are named after</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-08-29-the-amazing-people-streets-at-teachers-estate-are-named-after/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 23:30:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-08-29-the-amazing-people-streets-at-teachers-estate-are-named-after/</guid>
      <description>The Teacher&#39;s Estate is a private housing estate, named so because it was an area where government school teachers lived. This area have very interesting street names. All of the street names were named after an Asian philosopher and poet. In total, there are 7 historical figures that the roads were named after. Here&#39;s a list of them.
Omar Khayyam Avenue - named after Ghiyath ad-Din Abu I-Fath Omar Ibn Ibrahim Khayyam Neishapuri also known as Omar Khayyam</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solution to when none of your Mac accounts work and you can&#39;t login to your computer</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-08-29-solution-to-when-none-of-your-mac-accounts-work-and-you-cant-login-to-your-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 16:54:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-08-29-solution-to-when-none-of-your-mac-accounts-work-and-you-cant-login-to-your-computer/</guid>
      <description>So I had a very peculiar problem yesterday when I had to setup a Mac for a new user. The only problem was, I could not login to the admin account. That was strange. We provision accounts remotely using JumpCloud, allowing user credentials to be provisioned to individual systems. It allows me greater efficiency to onboard and offboard users.
What happened was the Mac has been inactive for 5 months. For some reason, it couldn&#39;t validate my password even though it was the correct one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Progressing with Tech</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-08-15-progressing-with-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 11:06:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-08-15-progressing-with-tech/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve been invited as a Table Host where I&#39;ll answer your questions about the Tech industry one-to-one, this Saturday, 19 August 2017, 10am-1.30pm.
Suitable for students, fresh graduates, working adults, mid-career professionals, stay-at-home mothers, anyone and everyone keen to learn more about tech! PPIS is working with The Codette Project to highlight the ease of access into the world of technology for your personal and professional use.
Apart from myself as a Table Host, there will also be a Panel Discussion with Member of Parliament, Mr Saktiandi Supaat and some of my friends from the Tech Industry, Liyana Sulaiman (Gimmie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordCamp Singapore 2017</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-07-27-20171028-wordcamp-singapore-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 15:03:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-07-27-20171028-wordcamp-singapore-2017/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve submitted my proposal to speak at WordCamp Singapore 2017 and hopefully accepted, I&#39;ll give insights into the State of the Woo regionally and globally.
Date: Saturday, 28 October 2017
Time: TBC
Venue: Suntec City Convention Centre
Topic Title: How WooCommerce is being disrupted by Shopify and why it will rapidly lose market share
Topic Description: WooCommerce is the most deployed eCommerce shopping cart platform in the world. But catching up closely is the world&#39;s most popular hosted eCommerce shopping cart - Shopify.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduates Tea 2017</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-07-27-20170820-graduates-tea-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 00:05:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-07-27-20170820-graduates-tea-2017/</guid>
      <description>Date: Sunday, 20 August 2017
10.30am to 2.30pm
Convention Centre@Suntec City
Register here: https://www.eventbrite.sg/e/mendaki-club-graduates-tea-2017-registration-35432282912
I&#39;ve been invited as a Table Host and will be sharing my experiences as an entrepreneur, technologist and E-Commerce hero. I&#39;ll help answer your questions about business and entrepreneurship, the software engineer career and E-Commerce insights. Feel free to give me an elevator pitch. Alongside me will be my wife, who is also invited as a Table Host, and she will be sharing her experiences as an educator, civil servant, and scholar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start With Why</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-06-15-start-with-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 16:13:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-06-15-start-with-why/</guid>
      <description>Great concept. I apply it in my daily life. The book seems to reiterate the Why in every chapter though. There is some extrapolation of the Golden Circle but it keeps coming back to Why. Probably the author&#39;s way of emphasising it&#39;s importance.
The stories are a bit long and may seem to look like fluff. But there&#39;s actually meat on this book. Just that the simple concept would take better articulation to present its points.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standards Adoption Workshop - TR46:2016 Last Mile Delivery - eCommerce Data Interchange</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-05-25-20170524-standards-adoption-workshop-tr462016-last-mile-delivery-ecommerce-data-interchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 16:09:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-05-25-20170524-standards-adoption-workshop-tr462016-last-mile-delivery-ecommerce-data-interchange/</guid>
      <description>I was the final speaker for the workshop standing among other contemporaries in the Logistics Tech industry. I recounted our experience adopting the TR46 standard into our TMS and elaborated the productivity gains as a result of the standards adoption. Many attendees later asked me questions on adopting the standards and the application of last mile technology in their processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a company with the right values</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-02-05-building-a-company-with-the-right-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 00:08:03 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-02-05-building-a-company-with-the-right-values/</guid>
      <description>To determine the company&#39;s success, it&#39;s not the technology or the team you assemble that matters most. Having built 4 businesses before and being part of 3 startups, my observations and experiences have made me discover that a company&#39;s values are what will make a company successful.
As an employee, one might not care about a company&#39;s mission, vision and values. It may seem like a piece of decoration and never taken seriously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deen &amp; Dunia - Designing bright Muslim professionals by Brothers of NUS</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/deen-dunia-designing-bright-muslim-professionals-by-brothers-of-nus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 22:44:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/deen-dunia-designing-bright-muslim-professionals-by-brothers-of-nus/</guid>
      <description>Venue: LT33 @ S17
The Prophet Muhammad (p.b.u.h) was asked what type of earning was best, and he replied, “A man’s work with his hands and every (lawful) business transaction.”
Entrepreneurs play an important role in our society, especially if one were to go back to the times of the Sahabahs and the Golden Age of Islam. However, in today’s day and age, being an entrepreneur, especially for a Muslim, is rarely an option when looking at a career path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Young and Malay: Growing up in Multicultural Malaysia</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/young-and-malay-growing-up-in-multicultural-malaysia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 17:02:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/young-and-malay-growing-up-in-multicultural-malaysia/</guid>
      <description>Edited by Ooi Kee Beng and Wan Hamidi Hamid, this book is a collection of essays, some anecdotal, others academic, of the viewpoints of ordinary Malaysians who identify themselves as Malay, on their life stories that shaped their perspectives in growing up in a multi-cultural nation, whilst coming to terms with their ethnic identity that forces them into boxes.
I picked up this book in Penang, at the GerakBudaya bookstore, apparently quite famous among those who read Malaysian literature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Career&#43;Tech Workshop by Mendaki Club</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-02-04-careertech-workshop-by-mendaki-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2016 22:26:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-02-04-careertech-workshop-by-mendaki-club/</guid>
      <description>Saturday, December 10, 2016
10am to 12pm
IMDA Labs@NDC
REGISTER TODAY: https://goo.gl/forms/GMa6frKNC2UYK1v73
Career+Tech explores how technology has impacted today&#39;s career landscape and how we can ride the &#34;tech wave&#34;.
Programme:
[1000-1040] Hands-on Activity by iCommerce Asia
&amp;gt; Learn the inner workings of the E-commerce supply chain from click to doorstep, through an interactive hands-on session by iCommerce Asia.
[1040-1100] Social Discussion by VoidDeck Ventures
&amp;gt; Together with tech enthusiasts, discuss how one can enhance their professional skill sets, and help the community embrace technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMP Learning Festival</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-02-04-20161022-amp-learning-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 22:53:41 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/2017-02-04-20161022-amp-learning-festival/</guid>
      <description>Date: Saturday, 22nd October 2016
Venue: Singapore University of Technology and Design
I will be sharing my life experience of starting a business in the technology world with school students ages 11 and up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malays represented as President, or a President that represents all?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/malays-represented-as-president-or-a-president-that-represents-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 16:18:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/malays-represented-as-president-or-a-president-that-represents-all/</guid>
      <description>Several years ago I shared how the government would back a Malay candidate for President after Nathan. The 2011 PE was an all Tan affair. However, the recent EP Commission has made clear the government&#39;s intention of a minority president from time to time.
Traditionally, Speakers of Parliament would likely be proposed as presidential candidates. Thus, since Abdullah Tarmugi and Halimah Yaacob&#39;s appointments as Speaker, I had been expecting one of them to be backed by government as their choice for President.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Startups By Muslims In Singapore You Need To Know This Ramadhan</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/7-muslim-startups-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2016 13:49:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/7-muslim-startups-singapore/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing Intelligently</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/pricing-intelligently/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2015 13:26:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/pricing-intelligently/</guid>
      <description>Pricing is the entire business. If you don&#39;t get pricing right, your business will not make it.
I&#39;ve often been told, Hazrul - you are expensive. Perhaps I&#39;ve worked with Chinese companies for quite long. I think it&#39;s ridiculous to price lower just because I&#39;m a Malay. It makes no sense. Why is there a market value for being of a particular race?
The first time I priced wrongly was when I first started work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lessons to ensure success for mobile payments in SE Asia.</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/lessons-to-ensure-success-for-mobile-payments-in-se-asia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 23:46:47 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/lessons-to-ensure-success-for-mobile-payments-in-se-asia/</guid>
      <description>A few years ago, I joined my friend&#39;s company to build a mobile payments solution for in-app payments in games. We were pretty much pioneering that space in SE Asia and had at the time secured Series A funding from Singtel and Stream Global. However, eventually the company didn&#39;t make it.
Go down to the base level
The lessons I&#39;ve learnt about mobile payment companies are that you have to go down to the base level and build your own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My experience applying for MaGiC&#39;s MAP</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/my-experience-applying-for-magics-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 11:31:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/my-experience-applying-for-magics-map/</guid>
      <description>In May 2015, I applied to join MAP, an accelerator programme by MaGiC.
A program to accelerate startups to be investment-ready in 4 months, and to build a strong ASEAN startup community by cultivating ASEAN relationships
 This was the first time I decided to apply for an accelerator and funding from VCs. We had to post a 90 second elevator pitch on Youtube along with an online submission about our startup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More public holidays may be better</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/more-public-holidays-may-be-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/more-public-holidays-may-be-better/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HalalOnClick, a halal food delivery service in Singapore.</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/halalonclick-com-a-halal-food-delivery-service-in-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:37:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/halalonclick-com-a-halal-food-delivery-service-in-singapore/</guid>
      <description>The first in our installations of tech startups in the Muslim world, halalonclick.com was created and founded by Muslims living in Singapore, a non-Muslim country. We stumbled across this gem from one of our friend&#39;s Facebook postings, and while its start has been small and quiet, its potential to rock the halal food landscape is massive.

Unlike other consolidated halal dining initiatives in Singapore, this was going to be a hit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Day - A celebration of what exactly?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/national-day-a-celebration-of-what-exactly/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2013 05:27:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/national-day-a-celebration-of-what-exactly/</guid>
      <description>In order to build our future, we need to understand our past. Singapore never proclaimed independence from Malaysia, a territory it fought to unite with. On the other hand, the 9th of August was a result of PM Tunku Abdul Rahman&amp;rsquo;s convictions that the internal security of Malaysia required Singapore&amp;rsquo;s exit. PM Lee Kuan Yew did not rejoice on the 9th of August 1965. On the other hand, he wept, publicly, live on television.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Singapore&#39;s media should be the backbone of local football</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/why-singapores-media-should-be-the-backbone-of-local-football/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2013 11:53:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/why-singapores-media-should-be-the-backbone-of-local-football/</guid>
      <description>The S.League has started and to be honest, I am concerned that the media has not stepped in and support the league. Sure, StarHub has been sponsoring the LionsXII and the League Cup. But why hasn&#39;t MediaCorp or Singtel come in to throw their weight behind our national league?
The first headlines propping the Straits Times last week after the first couple of games before even the 1st round was over, was discussing the low attendance despite the new season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a collaborative user network for Open Source WordPress in Asia</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/building-a-collaborative-user-network-for-open-source-wordpress-in-asia/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 02:34:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/building-a-collaborative-user-network-for-open-source-wordpress-in-asia/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;
Ladies and Gentlemen
Esteemed guests, from Singapore and overseas.
Thank you very much for helping us make history. You are the first attendees to Singapore&#39;s inaugural WordCamp.
Before I begin, I would like you to spend a moment asking yourselves this question. Why are you here? What are you doing right now? Are you blogging? Updating your Facebook? Sending a tweet? Checking in? What are you doing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A public declaration of love</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-public-declaration-of-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2010 05:36:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-public-declaration-of-love/</guid>
      <description>I am not someone who typically blogs about my personal life, and if anything, my most mentionable public displays of affection are on Facebook, where if anything, the perspectives are private. I am someone deeply driven by love. I do things because I love doing them. And most of all, because I am in love.
Those who know me, especially my siblings, would know the destructive nature when my heart was crushed before, many years back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Melayu. Who are you?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/melayu-who-are-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2010 02:06:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/melayu-who-are-you/</guid>
      <description>Melayu. Who are you?
Bongkok atau Bebas?
Radikal atau Alim?
Riau atau Baku?
Mundur atau Maju?
Yang aku tahu, Melayu bukan satu.
Kau Melayu. Aku Melayu. Tapi samakah kita?
Kau pukul satu. Aku pukul dua.
Tak bertemu-temu. Kerana janji Melayu.
Aku Melayu sini. Kau Melayu sana.
Kau belajar di Singapura, tapi tetap jiwa Alor Setar.
Kau Melayu miskin. Aku Melayu fakir.
Melayu kaya? Oh. Dia anak pemerintah saja.
Aku Melayu terdidik.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Menyerah Mahkota</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/menyerah-mahkota/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2009 04:00:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/menyerah-mahkota/</guid>
      <description>Every morning reciting the pledge, repeating every word, instilled in me a belief of the greatness of this nation. When I grew up, everywhere I turned, I had friends of different races and faiths. I could go to the mainstream PAP kindergarten in the mornings and I also went to the mosque kindergarten in the afternoon. I was exposed to different customs and languages and I had the opportunity to bask in the rich multi-racial flavour of our nation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demi Tanahair</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/demi-tanahair/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2009 04:46:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/demi-tanahair/</guid>
      <description>The last stand
The enemy shelled relentlessly. &#34;Tuan! Peluru dah habis tuan!&#34;, shouted a private. Charlie company had ran out of ammo. Lieutenant Adnan knew the inevitable. They were outnumbered 10 to 1. The 1st and 2nd Regiment gave everything they had, frustrating the Japs, pushing them back to Reformatory Road. But the moment of no return had come. Lieutenant Adnan had a choice to make. It would be untruthful to say that he was glad to make that choice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tanah Tumpah Darah</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tanah-tumpah-darah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2009 04:06:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/tanah-tumpah-darah/</guid>
      <description>Marker at the entrance of Bukit Chandu memorial
Second Lieutenant Adnan Bin Saidi.
Lieutenant Abdullah Bin Saad.
Lieutenant Ariffin Bin Haji Sulaiman.
Lieutenant Ibrahim Bin Sidek.
Lieutenant Abdul Wahid Bin Mat Kidam.
These are just some of the names that no one knows, who fought, bled and died for this land. These are the officers of the Malay Regiment. These are the anak watan who lived a short life, but left a great legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Islamic Information with iAlif</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/get-islamic-information-with-ialif/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/media/get-islamic-information-with-ialif/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singaporean enough?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singaporean-enough/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2009 18:39:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singaporean-enough/</guid>
      <description>When I go to the coffeeshop to order a cup of coke, I am greeted by a China-girl, who can&#39;t speak an inch of English, and tried to mouth back my order in barely comprehensible mainland Mandarin. The local prata shop staff which resides in the coffeeshop, is constantly frustrated at her, to the point of bad-mouthing in terms I can only say are ungracious. They&#39;ve tried so hard to communicate, telling her in English, that the used plates are to be placed inside the bin, not on their counters, but to no avail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Malay Story</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/the-malay-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2009 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/the-malay-story/</guid>
      <description>The following is a speech I gave in the presence of attendees of the &amp;ldquo;Melayu 2.0&amp;rdquo; meetup, an interest group supported by Mendaki that sought to engage the community to write a better future for Singapore Malays.
Dear friends.
In the past 10 years of Malay history, our community has seen through many challenges that has made our progress difficult and minute. When we ask ourselves, what has the Malay people achieved, there is little that we can be proud of.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halal - Another Feared Idea</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/halal-another-feared-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2008 22:14:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/halal-another-feared-idea/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A tale of 3 people from 3 nations</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-tale-of-3-people-from-3-nations-ethnicity-and-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2007 22:14:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/a-tale-of-3-people-from-3-nations-ethnicity-and-culture/</guid>
      <description>This would be a basi entry coz Ramadan was so 5 days ago. But I wanted to blog about the time I spent roaming around Geylang with Crystal and her friends. The only reason why I had not written about it was because I didn&#39;t snap enough good pics on those days, and for the life of me, I can&#39;t seem to remember one of her friend&#39;s name.
But I&#39;ll write about it anyway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Prayer Places Locater Screencast</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singapore-prayer-places-locater-screencast.html/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2007 05:21:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singapore-prayer-places-locater-screencast.html/</guid>
      <description>Now I&#39;ve been getting questions about this app. Everyone&#39;s wondering where can they find it. The bad news is, not so soon. I don&#39;t have a place to host this yet. The good news is, I created a screencast so that people can preview the power of Google Maps + a little bit of ingenuity from yours truly.
I hope this video will help you to visualise what SPPL is about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Singapore Prayer Places Locater 1.0 Beta Preview</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singapore-prayer-places-locater-10-beta-preview/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2007 05:34:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/singapore-prayer-places-locater-10-beta-preview/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve finished coding SPPL version 1.0. This is the Beta which I completed in a matter of 3 or 4 days. This application allows the user to search for the nearest mosque or musolla from his specified location. If you&#39;re a forgetful klutz like I am, or get intimidated by tall buildings or is in a huff but is not familliar with the area and so have no idea where the nearest prayer place is, SPPL is for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally getting the hang of Ruby on Rails</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/finally-getting-the-hang-of-ruby-on-rails/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2007 03:38:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/finally-getting-the-hang-of-ruby-on-rails/</guid>
      <description>After several hours messing with code and 1038482308483028 tutorials online, I finally got it! Behold!
Prayer Places Locater 1.0 (Alpha), Stable
My first proper RoR app. It&#39;s half done. I&#39;ll let you know when it&#39;s ready to launch. And I&#39;ll even write a tutorial here in due time for those developers that want to get a start on RoR. It&#39;s quite a fascinating language and framework. It has a lot of advantages over .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Friday at a quaint little mosque in Eunos</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/friday-at-a-quaint-little-mosque-in-eunos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 01:17:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/friday-at-a-quaint-little-mosque-in-eunos/</guid>
      <description>I find that I know so little about Singapore and it&#39;s hidden finds. Last Friday, I had my Friday prayers in a little known mosque hidden deep inside the private estates of Eunos. Masjid Al Abdul Razak appears to be a mosque of much history, with a architecture that resembles Yemeni/Saudi culture fused with less modern materials like zinc for a rustic, kampong feel.
Masjid Al Abdul Razak, a priceless heritage</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will You?</title>
      <link>//www.hazrulazhar.com/will-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2007 04:52:21 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//www.hazrulazhar.com/will-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ah yes. I know this is going to be a &lt;em&gt;basi&lt;/em&gt; entry. But I had a commitment to write this. I&#39;d like to share with my international friends, the story of this little red dot (as popularised by former Indonesian Head-of-State, President Habibie), on our &lt;a title=&#34;NDP 2007 Website&#34; href=&#34;http://www.ndp.org.sg/&#34;&gt;42nd year of independence&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I watched the spectacular &lt;a title=&#34;Watch NDP on demand!&#34; href=&#34;http://www.ndp.org.sg/multimedia/webcast/index.html&#34;&gt;celebrations from home on the Internet&lt;/a&gt;. Before I left for Jakarta, honestly, I didn&#39;t see much in Singapore that I wanted to be associated with. I would prefer a life in Australia (I still do). But coming home from Indonesia helped me to better appreciate the little things I put up with growing up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&#34;alignnone size-full wp-image-442&#34; src=&#34;//www.hazrulazhar.com/uploads/2007/09/dsc000581.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; width=&#34;384&#34; height=&#34;512&#34; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Packed road leading to Marina Bay&lt;a title=&#34;Packed road leading to Marina Bay&#34; href=&#34;http://hazrulazhar.com/wp-content/uploads/2007/09/dsc00058.JPG&#34;&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>